Felix Pacheco

React Developer Ssr.

Goal: Settle in a company where I can offer solutions applying my knowledge, sharing new experiences and keep growing as a professional and human being.

Education

System Engineer Santa María University Caracas / From March 2015 to October 2020 Mobile app development **SavePhone** to opt for the title of Engineering.

Bachelor Degree U.E.P Colegio San José Guatire / From September 2000 to July 2014

Work experience

Tech

Node IS

React Developer Ssr. Brocsoft Uruguay (Remoto desde Caracas) / Since November 2021

React Developer Ssr. Wadara Servicios Tecnológicos Caracas, Venezuela / From May 2021 to November 2021

React Developer ServiSenior Santiago - Chile (Remoto desde Caracas) / From September 2020 to April 2021

React Native Developer Jr. Anincubator Caracas / From June 2019 to September 2020

"iBeen" development, a mobile application to discover and sharing new places around the world.

Web Developer Jr. Ezgmz Caracas / From July 2018 to December 2018 React Developer Jr.

HTML

CSS3

Javascript

Git

React

React-Native

Cypress (UT)

React Testing Library (UT)

Next JS

Typescript



devfex.19@gmail.com

Caracas, VE

+58 414-3293929

https://felixpacheco.vercel.app/en

& Venezuelan

26 years old

ᄓ

Languages

Spanish

English

Skills

Logic

Planning

Organization

Responsability and perseverance

Hobbies

Personal Projects

Sports Futbol

Exercise

Interested in

Next IS

Unit Testing

Node JS

Typescript

Mongo DB

Courses and certifications

React Native Platzi Caracas, Venezuela / From June 2019 to August 2019

Online

Redux Platzi Caracas, Venezuela / From April 2019 to May 2019

Online

React Router Platzi Caracas, Venezuela / May 2019

Online

React JS Platzi Caracas, Venezuela / From April 2019 to June 2019

Online

Arquitecto Front-End Platzi Caracas, Venezuela / From January 2019 to March 2019

Online

HTML y CSS Platzi Caracas, Venezuela / March 2019

Online

Desarrollo Web Online Platzi Caracas, Venezuela / February 2019

Online

Fundamentos de Javascript Platzi Caracas, Venezuela / February 2019

Online

Responsive Design Platzi Caracas, Venezuela / From January 2019 to February 2019

Online

Git y Github Platzi Caracas, Venezuela / January 2019

Online

Diseño Web Profesional El Curso Completo, Práctico y Desde Cero Udemy Caracas,

Venezuela / From February 2017 to October 2017

Online

@Felixmp7

in @felix-pacheco-30

@felixmp_a

Assets

Proactivity and participation

I like to feel that I am part of the the project, not only who develop it.

Leadership

I really like to being a reference, teaching and support my coworkers.

Team working

I like to achieve goals together and enjoy the road to success.

About me

Hi, I'm Felix. I'm a System Engineer from Caracas, Venezuela. I'm 26 years old and I have been working as a React Developer since 2019. I'm able to describe myself for being really honest, detailed, responsible and active in terms of work. I'm into doing things well.I consider myself as a person who never gives up, I always try to overcome the obstacles and I try to stand out from others. I always try to help, support and learn from my coworkers to keep growing as a professional and as a human being.